A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13 FA285
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Titles, 9
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume I and II (Permission to Quote), January 29, 1959-September 30, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 977)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume II (Correspondence), October 21, 1959-September 26, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 978)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume II (Distribution), September 26, 1960-January 10, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 979)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume II (Editorial), February 3, 1959-April 28, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 980)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume II (Editorial), May 3, 1960-October 20, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 981)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume II (Illustrations), April 4, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 982)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume II (Production), June 2, 1952-April 4, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 983)
  - "Coronary Heart Disease In Young Adults" - Correspondence, March 29, 1949-May 28, 1951 (Box 82, Folder 984)
  - "Coronary Heart Disease In Young Adults" - Correspondence, June 15, 1951-February 1, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 985)
  - "Coronary Heart Disease In Young Adults" - Printing, April 23, 1953-April 22, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 986)
  - "Coronary Heart Disease In Young Adults" - Sales Promotion, October 19, 1953-January 21, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 987)
  - "Cousins and Strangers" - Correspondence, August 9, 1954-March 22, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 988)
  - "Cousins and Strangers" - Printing, October 21, 1954-December 19, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 989)
  - "Cousins and Strangers" - Sales Promotion, August 9, 1955-August 3, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 990)
  - "Criminal Careers in Retrospect" - Correspondence, February 29, 1940-March 23, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 991)
  - "Criminal Careers in Retrospect" - Printing, April 21, 1943-May 4, 1953 (Box 83, Folder 992)
  - "Criminal Youth and the Borstal System" - Correspondence, October 4, 1940-February 4, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 993)
  - "Dentistry" - Circulation and Distribution, June 14, 1946-October 30, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 994)
  - "Dentistry" - Correspondence, November 30, 1945-September 20, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 995)
  - "Dentistry" - Printing, January 10, 1946-September 16, 1946 (Box 84, Folder 996)
  - "Diagnosis of Uterine Cancer" - Circulation and Distribution, April 8, 1943-June 21, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 997)
  - "Diagnosis of Uterine Cancer" - Correspondence, August 3, 1948-October 24, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 998)
  - "Diagnosis of Uterine Cancer" - Insert of the Reprint (Dr. Papanicolaou Article), August 23, 1943-January 27, 1944 (Box 84, Folder 999)
  - "Diagnosis of Uterine Cancer" - Printing (First and Second Editions), September 11, 1941-June 5, 1945 (Box 84, Folder 1000)
  - "Diagnosis of Uterine Cancer" - Printing (Third and Fourth Editions), October 15, 1946-March 1, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1001)
  - "Directory of British Fellows 1925-1950", August 19, 1949-March 4, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 1002)
  - "Directory of British and Continental Fellows 1925-1955", November 5, 1953-January 17, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 1003)
  - "Directory of Commonwealth Fund Fellows 1925-1937", February 26, 1938-November 18, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 1004)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Application and Announcement Forms (Harkness Fellowships), February 20, 1952-1961 (Box 84, Folder 1005)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Christmas Card (Harkness House), June 18, 1952-June 28, 1955 (Box 84, Folder 1006)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Christmas Letter, August 7, 1954-November 15, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 1007)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Christmas Letter, August 7, 1954-November 15, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 1008)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Christmas Letter, August 7, 1954-November 15, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 1009)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Christmas Letter, August 7, 1954-November 15, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 1010)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Face Sheets, October 28, 1959-January 3, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 1011)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Fellowship Award Letters/Certification Letter, March 4, 1952-December 6, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 1012)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Fellowships Expense Ledger Cards, May 14, 1953-June 27, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1013)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Handbook for Harkness Fellows, March 2, 1951-January 13, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1014)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Handbook for Harkness Fellows, March 2, 1951-January 13, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1015)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Harkness Fellowships Booklet, August 12, 1963-August 3, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 1016)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Inserts for Handbook for the Commonwealth Fund Fellows, January 28, 1954-March 3, 1954 (Box 85, Folder 1017)
  - Division of International Fellowships - Questionnaire and Announcements for Commonwealth Fund Fellows, May 24-31, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 1018)
  - "The Doctor and the Difficult Child" - Correspondence, April 8, 1932-December 17, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 1019)
  - Printing of Dummying Sheets, July 2, 1953-August 31, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 1020)
  - "Early American Land Companies" - Correspondence, March 23, 1936-January 19, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 1021)
  - "Ecology of Health" - Circulation and Distribution, October 27, 1949-April 30, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 1022)
  - "Ecology of Health" - Correspondence, April 25, 1949-January 14, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 1023)
  - "Ecology of Health" - Printing, June 22, 1949-November 1, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 1024)
  - Editorial Slips, December 23, 1953-February 19, 1954 (Box 86, Folder 1025)
  - "Educational Achievement of Problem Children" - Printing, July 17, 1928-May 5, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 1026)
  - "Effect of Advancing Age Upon the Human Spinal Cord" - Correspondence, August 14, 1956-August 15, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 1027)
  - "Effect of Advancing Age Upon the Human Spinal Cord" - Distribution, February 28, 1957-August 5, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 1028)
  - "Effect of Advancing Age Upon the Human Spinal Cord" - Editorial, October 30, 1957-September 3, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 1029)
  - "Effect of Advancing Age Upon the Human Spinal Cord" - Production, February 25, 1958-January 15, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 1030)
  - "Effects of Brain Injury in Man" - Correspondence, May 23, 1957-February 1, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 1031)
  - "Eight Years of Public Health Work" - Correspondence, January 16, 1942-June 28, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 1032)
  - "Eight Years of Public Health Work" - Printing, November 20, 1945-July 1, 1946 (Box 86, Folder 1033)
  - "The English Business Company After the Bubble Act" - Correspondence, November 19, 1936-May 12, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 1034)
  - "The English Business Company After the Bubble Act" - Printing, November 9, 1937-August 4, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 1035)
  - "The Envelope" - Circulation and Distribution, February 23, 1950-March 8, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 1036)
  - "The Envelope" - Correspondence, September 17, 1937-October 3, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 1037)
  - "The Envelope" - Correspondence, September 17, 1937-October 3, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 1038)
  - "The Envelope" - Printing, April 11, 1949-December 16, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 1039)
  - "Episodic Behavioral Disorders" (Russell R. Monroe) [Grant-in-Aid], May 30, 1967-October 5, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 1040)
  - "Epithelia of Women's Reproductive Organs" - Circulation and Distribution, February 2, 1948-February 8, 1951 (Box 87, Folder 1041)
  - "Epithelia of Women's Reproductive Organs" - Correspondence, September 28, 1942-November 5, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1042)
  - "Epithelia of Women's Reproductive Organs" - Correspondence, September 28, 1942-November 5, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 1043)
  - "Epithelia of Women's Reproductive Organs" - Printing, February 3, 1944-March 1, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 1044)
  - "Essentials of the Diagnostic Examination" (John B. Youman) - Correspondence, January 6, 1936-April 10, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 1045)
  - "Essentials of the Diagnostic Examination" (John B. Youman) - Correspondence, January 6, 1936-April 10, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 1046)
  - "Essentials of the Diagnostic Examination" (John B. Youman) - Correspondence, January 6, 1936-April 10, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 1047)
  - "Essentials of the Diagnostic Examination" (John B. Youman) - Printing First through Fifth Editions, May 27, 1938-November 21, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 1048)
  - "Essentials of the Diagnostic Examination" (John B. Youman) - Printing First through Fifth Editions, May 27, 1938-November 21, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 1049)
  - "The Etiology of Trachoma" (Louis A. Julianelle) - Correspondence, December 18, 1929-October 19, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 1050)
  - "The Etiology of Trachoma" (Louis A. Julianelle) - Printing, November 4, 1937-November 17, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 1051)
  - "Explorations into the Nature of the Living Cell" (Edward L. Chambers) - Correspondence, April 17, 1959-May 5, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 1052)
  - "Explorations into the Nature of the Living Cell" (Edward L. Chambers) - Distribution, June 2, 1950-May 5, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 1053)
  - "Explorations into the Nature of the Living Cell" (Edward L. Chambers) - Editorial, August 3, 1959-May 3, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 1054)
  - "Explorations into the Nature of the Living Cell" (Edward L. Chambers) - Permission to Quote, November 9, 1959-August 10, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 1055)
  - "Explorations into the Nature of the Living Cell" (Edward L. Chambers) - Production, September 16, 1959-June 6, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 1056)
  - "Federal Trade Commission" - Correspondence and Printing, January 30, 1924-March 18, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 1057)
  - Fellowships and Awards in the Health Field, January 13, 1960-June 24, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 1058)
  - "Felony and Misdemeanor", January 14, 1936-June 20, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 1059)
  - "Field Unit in Local Public Health Service", November 19, 1936-December 28, 1938 (Box 88, Folder 1060)
  - "Five Years in Fargo", October 28, 1928-November 26, 1951 (Box 88, Folder 1061)
  - "Foster Home Care for Mental Patients" - Correspondence, May 16, 1940-July 16, 1951 (Box 88, Folder 1062)
  - "Foster Home Care for Mental Patients" - Printing, October 22, 1943-February 14, 1949 (Box 88, Folder 1063)
  - "Foundations for A Science of Personality" - Correspondence, May 3, 1940-January 26, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1064)
  - "Foundations for A Science of Personality" - Printing, September 12, 1941-May 27, 1958 (Box 89, Folder 1065)
  - "Functional Endocrinology from Birth through Adolescence" (Nathan Talbot) - Correspondence, November 7, 1946-March 10, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1066)
  - "Functional Endocrinology from Birth through Adolescence" (Nathan Talbot) - Correspondence, November 7, 1946-March 10, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1067)
  - "Functional Endocrinology from Birth through Adolescence" (Nathan Talbot) - Correspondence, November 7, 1946-March 10, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1068)
  - "Functional Endocrinology from Birth through Adolescence" (Nathan Talbot) - Permission to Quote, February 29, 1948-October 25, 1951 (Box 89, Folder 1069)
  - "Functional Endocrinology from Birth through Adolescence" (Nathan Talbot) - Permission to Quote, February 29, 1948-October 25, 1951 (Box 89, Folder 1070)
  - "Functional Endocrinology from Birth through Adolescence" (Nathan Talbot) - Printing and Reprinting, March 31, 1951-July 3, 1957 (Box 89, Folder 1071)
  - "Functional Endocrinology from Birth through Adolescence" (Nathan Talbot) - Sales Promotion, May 4, 1951-February 11, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 1072)
  - "Fundamentals of Roentgenology" - Correspondence, July 27, 1961-May 2, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 1073)
  - "Fundamentals of Roentgenology" - Distribution, October 26, 1962-April 22, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 1074)
  - "Fundamentals of Roentgenology" - Duplicates of Key to Master List of Illustrations for Mr. Stratton, No Date (Box 90, Folder 1075)
  - "Fundamentals of Roentgenology" - Production, June 2, 1961-January 14, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 1076)
  - "A Future for Preventative Medicine" - Circulation and Distribution, October 29, 1945-February 7, 1947 (Box 90, Folder 1077)
  - "A Future for Preventative Medicine" - Correspondence, February 23, 1945-June 13, 1958 (Box 90, Folder 1078)
  - "A Future for Preventative Medicine" - Printing, June 26, 1945-June 27, 1947 (Box 90, Folder 1079)
  - General Mailing to Physicians (Sales Promotion), November 13, 1951-December 27, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 1080)
  - "Genetic Basis of Morphological Variation" (Richard H. Osborne and Francis V. DeGeorge) - Correspondence, November 30, 1956-December 19, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 1081)
  - "Genetic Basis of Morphological Variation" (Richard H. Osborne and Francis V. DeGeorge) - Editorial, November 19, 1957-September 8, 1959 (Box 90, Folder 1082)
  - "Genetic Basis of Morphological Variation" (Richard H. Osborne and Francis V. DeGeorge) - Production, March 30, 1959-June 6, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 1083)
  - "Genetic Basis of Morphological Variation" (Richard H. Osborne and Francis V. DeGeorge) - Sales Promotion, May 18, 1959-December 21, 1959 (Box 90, Folder 1084)
  - "Government in Public Health" - Circulation and Distribution, May 29, 1945-April 30, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 1085)
  - "Government in Public Health" - Correspondence, December 21, 1944-October 8, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 1086)
  - "Government in Public Health" - Printing, January 8, 1945-April 16, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 1087)
  - "Group Psychotherapy Studies in the Methodology of Research and Therapy" - Correspondence, June 24, 1944-September 18, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1088)
  - "Group Psychotherapy Studies in the Methodology of Research and Therapy" - Correspondence, June 24, 1944-September 18, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 1089)
  - "Group Psychotherapy Studies in the Methodology of Research and Therapy" - Index, July 9, 1952-January 23, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 1090)
  - "Group Psychotherapy Studies in the Methodology of Research and Therapy" - Printing, July 18, 1951-February 23, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 1091)
  - "Group Psychotherapy Studies in the Methodology of Research and Therapy" - Sales Promotion, August 23, 1952-September 11, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 1092)
  - "Biography of Edward Stephen Harkness", August 20, 1950-August 31, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 1093)
  - "Health and Medical Care in New York City" - Correspondence, February 10, 1956-June 18, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 1094)
  - "Health and Medical Care in New York City" - Distribution, September 17, 1956-June 28, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 1095)
  - "Health and Medical Care in New York City" - Editorial, July 5, 1956-March 18, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 1096)
  - "Health and Medical Care in New York City" - Production, June 6, 1956-September 9, 1957 (Box 92, Folder 1097)
  - "Health Center Buildings" - Correspondence, December 2, 1947-September 20, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 1098)
  - "Health Center Buildings" - Printing, January 23, 1946-May 5, 1948 (Box 92, Folder 1099)
  - "The Health Insurance Movement in the United States" (Nathan Sinai) - Circulation and Distribution, September 26, 1946-February 13, 1951 (Box 92, Folder 1100)
  - "The Health Insurance Movement in the United States" (Nathan Sinai) - Correspondence, June 26, 1945-August 8, 1951 (Box 92, Folder 1101)
  - "The Health Insurance Movement in the United States" (Nathan Sinai) - Printing, June 13, 1945-February 8, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 1102)
  - "Heredity in Uterine Cancer" - Correspondence, July 17, 1947-October 22, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 1103)
  - "Heredity in Uterine Cancer" - Correspondence, July 17, 1947-October 22, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 1104)
  - "Heredity in Uterine Cancer" - Printing, August 28, 1950-October 13, 1955 (Box 92, Folder 1105)
  - "Historical Sketch" (Roger A. Crane), March 9, 1962-October 29, 1963 (Box 92, Folder 1106)
  - "The History of Sir Sigfried", September 11, 1958-October 14, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 1107)
  - "Hospital Care in the United States" - Circulation and Distribution, August 1, 1946-February 2, 1948 (Box 92, Folder 1108)
  - "Hospital Care in the United States" - Correspondence, April 5, 1946-November 15, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 1109)
  - "Hospital Care in the United States" - Printing, October 17, 1946-March 14, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 1110)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Correspondence, May 25, 1938-October 25, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1111)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Permission to Quote, September 24, 1940-July 16, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 1112)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Permission to Quote, September 24, 1940-July 16, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 1113)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Permission to Quote, September 24, 1940-July 16, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 1114)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Permission to Quote, September 24, 1940-July 16, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 1115)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Permission to Quote, September 24, 1940-July 16, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 1116)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Permission to Reference, September 10, 1947-April 10, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 1117)
  - "The Hospital in Modern Society" - Printing, November 5, 1942-January 6, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 1118)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments" - Circulation and Distribution, July 14, 1948-February 19, 1951 (Box 94, Folder 1119)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments" - Correspondence, June 6, 1944-August 16, 1951 (Box 94, Folder 1120)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments" - Permission to Reference, October 30, 1947-May 18, 1948 (Box 94, Folder 1121)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments" - Permission to Reference, October 30, 1947-May 18, 1948 (Box 94, Folder 1122)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments" - Permission to Reference, October 30, 1947-May 18, 1948 (Box 94, Folder 1123)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments" - Permission to Reference, October 30, 1947-May 18, 1948 (Box 94, Folder 1124)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments" - Printing, January 15, 1948-April 30, 1958 (Box 94, Folder 1125)
  - "Housemother's Guide" - Circulation and Distribution, December 13, 1946-January 22, 1947 (Box 94, Folder 1126)
  - "Housemother's Guide" - Correspondence, February 5, 1945-December 17, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 1127)
  - "Housemother's Guide" - Printing, September 23, 1946-July 25, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 1128)
  - "Human Blood in New York City" - Correspondence, December 12, 1957-April 11, 1958 (Box 94, Folder 1129)
  - "Human Blood in New York City" - Distribution and Production, February 7, 1958-October 7, 1958 (Box 95, Folder 1130)
  - "Human Relationships in Public Health" - Circulation and Distribution, January 18, 1949-April 29, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 1131)
  - "Human Relationships in Public Health" - Correspondence, January 27, 1949-October 26, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 1132)
  - "Human Relationships in Public Health" - Printing, January 5, 1949-May 24, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 1133)
  - "Hunterdon Medical Center" - Correspondence, March 3, 1953-March 22, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 1134)
  - "Hunterdon Medical Center" - Permissions, April 20, 1955-February 27, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 1135)
  - "Hunterdon Medical Center" - Printing, September 14, 1955-July 27, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 1136)
  - "Hunterdon Medical Center" - Sales Promotion, November 22, 1955-September 10, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 1137)
  - "Hypertension and Hypertensive Disease" - Correspondence, November 13, 1942-July 11, 1951 (Box 95, Folder 1138)
  - "Hypertension and Hypertensive Disease" - Printing (First Edition), October 27, 1943-May 4, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 1139)
  - "Hypertension and Hypertensive Disease" - Printing (Second, Third and Fourth Editions), November 3, 1944-January 29, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 1140)
  - Information for Recipients of Advanced Medical Fellowships in the Health Field, February 2, 1956-March 6, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 1141)
  - "Influence of a Public Health Program on a Rural Community", April 4, 1940-July 10, 1940 (Box 96, Folder 1142)
  - "Insanity as a Defense in Criminal Law", November 5, 1930-September 25, 1931 (Box 96, Folder 1143)
  - Institute for Child Guidance - Reports, March 17, 1933-June 29, 1933 (Box 96, Folder 1144)
  - Institute for Child Guidance - Studies, September 29, 1930-May 6, 1931 (Box 96, Folder 1145)
  - "Insulin: Its Chemistry and Physiology", December 11, 1934 to September 15, 1944; October 15-20, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1146)
  - Internships and Residencies in New York City, November 23, 1933-September 28, 1951 (Box 96, Folder 1147)
  - "Interstate Commerce Commission", August 19, 1930-July 11, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 1148)
  - "An Introduction to Group Therapy" - Correspondence, January 23, 1941 to November 13, 1951; May 14-25, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 1149)
  - "An Introduction to Group Therapy" - Printing, December 24, 1942-May 28, 1947 (Box 96, Folder 1150)
  - "An Introduction to the Universal Serologic Reaction in Health and Disease" - Correspondence, 1930-1932, 1948-1953 (Box 96, Folder 1151)
  - "An Introduction to the Universal Serologic Reaction in Health and Disease" - Printing, May 19, 1950-May 4, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 1152)
  - "An Introduction to the Universal Serologic Reaction in Health and Disease" - Sales, November 14, 1950-May 5, 1951 (Box 96, Folder 1153)
  - Journal of Medical Education - Haggerty, Robert J. - "Family Medicine: A Teaching Program for Medical Students and Pediatric House Officers", July 20, 1961-August 10, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 1154)
  - Journal of Medical Education - Kennell, John H. - Paper on the Family Clinic at Western Reserve University, September 11, 1961-February 15, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 1155)
  - Journal of Medical Education - Lee, Peter V. - "Medical Schools and the Changing Times", May 10, 1960-April 26, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1156)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Commonwealth Fund, Grants Series, Box 181, Folder 1692.
  - Journal of Medical Education - Sonkin, L. - "Home Care in Medical Education", April 7, 1958-June 22, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 1157)
  - "Judicial Function in Federal Administrative Agencies", May 7, 1934-January 23, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 1158)
  - "Juvenile Delinquents Grown Up" - Correspondence, 1937-1941, 1965, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 1159)
  - "Juvenile Delinquents Grown Up" - Distribution, March 10, 1939-April 19, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 1160)
  - "Juvenile Delinquents Grown Up" - Printing, 1939-1948, 1957-1958 (Box 97, Folder 1161)
  - Labels, October 30, 1951-November 13, 1951 (Box 97, Folder 1162)
  - "Later Criminal Careers" - Circularizing, April 21, 1937-September 13, 1937 (Box 97, Folder 1163)
  - "Later Criminal Careers" - Correspondence, 1933-1937, 1959-1965 (Box 97, Folder 1164)
  - "Later Criminal Careers" - Printing, 1937-1941, 1951 (Box 97, Folder 1165)
  - "Law Enforcement in Colonial New York", 1940-1948, 1969-1971 (Box 97, Folder 1166)
    See also Commonwealth Fund, Division of Publications, Box 57, Folder 616.
  - "Law of Evidence", September 30, 1927 (Box 97, Folder 1167)
  - "Legislative Regulation", November 11, 1930-June 4, 1932 (Box 97, Folder 1168)
  - "Liberal Arts and Medical Education" - Oberlin College, October 23, 1956-November 25, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 1169)
  - "Lobar Pneumonia and Serum Therapy", June 26, 1934-February 27, 1937 (Box 98, Folder 1170)
  - "Local Health Units for the Nation" - Correspondence and Distribution, 1944-1951, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 1171)
  - "Local Health Units for the Nation" - Printing, 1944-1946, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 1172)
  - "Longitudinal Studies of Child Personality: Abstracts with Index" - Correspondence, July 8, 1955-May 16, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 1173)
  - "Longitudinal Studies of Child Personality: Abstracts with Index" - Distribution, Editorial, Miscellaneous, January 2, 1958-March 23, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 1174)